I only have one real in my pocket and ninety days to
build a business from scratch
but I live on Chevette
and today is the day of the fourteen
7 truffles
face secret
is you use the lighting a little
that the added value is not in the product
and yes in the experience you provide
and I'll hide this and then I'll put crazy daddy in
can allow the child to play
yes or no
yes just register your application here
have a symbolic value
ten real
and this is how i see chocolate
this is my enrollment sheet
ha ha happy children's day
what is your name Matthew
due to children's day
we are doing some sporadic actions in the park
I don't know if you guys like hunting treasure
opa needs parental permission first
if you want to participate
I explain the dynamics
with parental supervision
and then those who want to have a QR code
o pix
and the final prize is a bunch of cocoa show chocolate
who wants to participate closed
will be treasure hunt
wants to participate who wants to participate is Gi
let's go on this treasure hunt
will begin
who else will
everything is already there
pay attention to the treasure pants
only worth in this field here ó
cannot go back there
1 2
3 and happy children's day
valid
run
run daddy and mommy
helps to look eh
there is already a child who is hot
power of attorney
post fart
bora bora
our these children are very slow
my god found
I don't know
but it seems that we have
there is a professional hunter named Alessandra here
let me see
calm has what is written in there
clap hands for Alessandra
Alexandra
congratulations
you won a chocolate kit
congratulations bat
three and already
thank you saw for participating
beat here
Too much time bristle brother
tamo together face
it's us vei
valeu bye bye
I'm crazy here
but it was good vei
ran out of chocolate
parents loved
children loved
dynamics
it's a way to sell without selling bro
value is already added to the experience
money in pocket and money
but i know yes no
bye bye Valeu
starving here bro
bye all good worth
from now on
i need to be more daring in this series
so i can make some quick money bro